I'm glad it's sunny again today.
今日も晴れて良かったね
yes.
はい
I didn't expect to spend the night with you.
一緒に一晩泊まれるとは思ってなかったからですよ
Did you know that there's a garden here?
ここ行ったらさ、なんか庭園があるの知ってる?
i don't know.
知らない
It's in the middle of this city.
この都会の真ん中にあるんだよ
Is that so?
そうなの?
If you go a long time ago, the grass in the morning is not good.
ずっと前に行ったら朝、草とかの方が良くない
I like the downtown feel.
下町っぽいのが好きなんだけど
In the future, which is better: a house, an apartment, or a single house?
将来、お家やマンションと一軒やどっちが良い?
I'll do one.
一軒やる
That's good, I'll do one.
良いよね、一軒やるのが
What is the configuration?
どういう構成なの?
Family structure.
家族構成とか
future.
将来の
Still look.
まだ見て
Will we become a family together?
一緒に家族になっちゃう?
I'm nervous.
緊張しちゃう
Looks like I'm going to their residence.
2人の居敷に行くみたいだね
結構
Hiro: Yes.
広 そう
It's like email.
メールみたい
How do you go?
どう行く?
Go like this, like this.
こう行って、こう
Try hitting the edge?
端を当たってみる?
There are quite a few people.
結構人がいる
You know this place.
知ってるんだね、こういう所ね
It doesn't seem like Tokyo.
東京じゃないみたい
I agree.
そうだ ね
I wonder if there are no carp?
鯉とかいないのかな?
There are some small fish.
なんか小さい魚いる
It's true, I'm seeing something.
ほんとだ、何か見てきてる
I agree.
そうだね
Beautiful, like maple leaves.
綺麗、もうみじとか
It's green though.
緑色だけど
When it turns red, it's beautiful again.
赤くなったらまたうちきれいだよね
Let's come back together when it turns red.
赤くなったらまた来ようよ、一緒に
I was here once before, and there was a snake there.
昔、ここ一回来てたんだけど、蛇がいたんだよね
I don't think now is the time.
今、この時期でないと思うけどね
What kind of snake is a snake?
蛇ってどんな蛇なの?
Spring is getting warmer, isn't it?
春とか暖かくなってきたじゃないの?
When it gets a little warmer.
もうちょっと暖かくなったら
If you see a snake at the beginning of the year, if you see it every year,
年の始まりに蛇見たら、毎年見たら、
I think I'll make money this year too.
今年も稼げるぜ、みたいな
Good, it's quirky.
いいね、癖ある
You got your hands on it, right?
手が入ったでしょ?
Looking at it from here, I don't understand it at all.
ここから見たら全然わかんない
It's a normal hotel.
普通のホテルなんだ
There was a proper garden.
ちゃんと庭園があったんだ
I got to see all kinds of delicious things,
いろんなおいしいもの見させられて、
Because I'm hungry.
お腹やばいからさ
Are you hungry?
お腹空いちゃった?
There's no way back there?
そこの帰りがない?
I feel like it was there somehow.
なんかそこにあった気がするんだよね
The common people will return there if the common people go.
庶民は庶民がいけばそこに戻ろう
It's quite big.
結構でかいね
Is this all you need?
これだけでいいのかな?
Are you okay.
大丈夫
That's all you need.
これだけでいい
amazing.
すごい
That's amazing.
すごいね
looks delicious.
美味しそう
This is a girl who likes sweet things.
これ甘いものが好きな女の子
Can I have a bite?
ちょっと食べていい?
It's quite flexible.
結構軟力がある
It's true.
本当だ
looks delicious.
美味しそう
Does it feel good?
いい感じ?
on second thoughts.
やっぱり
terrible.
やばい
That was fine over there.
あそこはこれでよかった
Are you okay.
大丈夫
Is this okay?
これでいいの?
thank you.
ありがと
Because it's time for this person to check out.
この人のチェックアウトの時間だから
How many times should I do it?
何回したらいいの?
Her breath is cool and cute.
鼻息涼しくてかわいい
You went back downstairs today, right?
今日は下に帰ってたよね?
As expected.
やっぱりそうだ
Why don't you go inside?
奥に行かない?
Can I take it away?
奪わせていい?
appear?
見える?
It's disordered.
乱れてる
cute.
可愛い
This is a heart.
これハートじゃん
Why is there a heart on the back?
なんで裏はハートなの?
i don't know.
知らない
There's nothing on the front, but the back looks like a heart.
表は何もないのに裏はハートみたいな
Can I take it away?
奪わせていい?
It's cold.
寒いんだもん
Because I wear them all the time.
いつも履いてるから
I'm a secretary.
秘書だもん
Such beautiful feet.
こんな綺麗な足
Is this the only one you wear?
こっちだけ履いてる?
nice.
いいね
That's amazing.
すごいよ
difficult?
難しい?
appear?
見える?
It's disordered.
乱れてる
Why not?
なんでないの?
No name.
名前なし
Does it just feel good?
気持ちいいだけ?
Can you squat down?
しゃがんでくれる?
Squat down?
しゃがんで?
Push it up like this.
こうやって押し上げて
It's cool to rub your back.
腰こすりかっこよ
It's just like that.
そのままだよ
It's twitching.
ピクピクになってる
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
Can't move?
動けない?
Put it in your mouth, Grandpa.
口に入れて、おじいち
I'm sure you can do it while sitting.
きっとも座りながらやって
Do it.
やって
Butt?
おしり?
Can I see it?
見 せてもらっていい?
amazing.
すごい
It's kind of wet here.
なんか濡れてる、ここ
Why are you wet?
なんで濡れてるの?
Can you do a cleaning blow job?
お掃除フェラーとかできるの?
Can I have it done?
やってもらっていい?
No?
やだ?
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
Can you do it?
できるの?
Is it just embarrassing?
恥ずかしいだけ?
If it's just embarrassing, I'll let you do it.
恥ずかしいだけならやらせるよ
I don't like it.
嫌だ
Do you have your own curls?
自分のまんじみとかついてる?
I don't like it.
嫌だ
Because it's easy.
やさしいから
Touch the chicken too.
チキンとも触って
Touch my dick.
ともとチンチン触って
I want to put it in again.
もう一回入れたいんだよね
Can I come in?
入れていい?
One more time.
もう一回
I have to jekk out, not too soon.
早くじゃなくて、ジェックアウトしかなきゃ
If I had a dick nearby, I might stand up.
近くにチンコ持ってたら立つかもしれない
Butt?
おしり?
This too.
これも
Maybe I can release it again.
もう一回出せるかも
child
こ
When would you like to see it?
いつ 見てほしい
I want you to see where I'm going.
行くところ見てほしい
Keep looking here.
ず っとここ見てて
good?
いい?
Please watch as I release it.
出すから見てて
Shall we go?
行くよ?
Shall I put it out?
出すよ?
Time has passed though.
時間過ぎちゃったけど
Is it okay?
大丈夫かな?